{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786717150","data":{"timestamp":" 946786717150"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_071828"," gameId":" 560cece6-f234-4b62-b2fb-edaa1f231213"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__story_32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Baadaye alipopata nafuu Rahim alituomba msamaha."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786752785","data":{"timestamp":" 946786752784"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_071828"," gameId":" cc0c032e-61dc-48b7-b644-85298adf5bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_nilijua_nilijua-alipata-magunia"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nilijua"," userResponse":" nilijua"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786758944","data":{"timestamp":" 946786758944"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_071828"," gameId":" cc0c032e-61dc-48b7-b644-85298adf5bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kayanja_kayanja-maswali-kikubwa"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kayanja"," userResponse":" kayanja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786766933","data":{"timestamp":" 946786766932"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_071828"," gameId":" cc0c032e-61dc-48b7-b644-85298adf5bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_mandazi_mandazi-michafu-kumpiga"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mandazi"," userResponse":" mandazi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786772589","data":{"timestamp":" 946786772589"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_071828"," gameId":" cc0c032e-61dc-48b7-b644-85298adf5bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_unywele_magozwe-haikuwa-unywele"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" unywele"," userResponse":" unywele"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786780069","data":{"timestamp":" 946786780068"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_071828"," gameId":" cc0c032e-61dc-48b7-b644-85298adf5bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_akaruka_akaruka-anasema-kitoweo"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" akaruka"," userResponse":" akaruka"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786785943","data":{"timestamp":" 946786785943"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_071828"," gameId":" cc0c032e-61dc-48b7-b644-85298adf5bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_kuliita_kuliita-kawaida-akapata"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" kuliita"," userResponse":" kuliita"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786792386","data":{"timestamp":" 946786792386"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_071828"," gameId":" cc0c032e-61dc-48b7-b644-85298adf5bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_alifika_wenyewe-alifika-refiloe"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" alifika"," userResponse":" alifika"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786799750","data":{"timestamp":" 946786799750"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_071828"," gameId":" cc0c032e-61dc-48b7-b644-85298adf5bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_akasema_akasema-ninajua-matunda"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" akasema"," userResponse":" akasema"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786813422","data":{"timestamp":" 946786813422"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_071828"," gameId":" cc0c032e-61dc-48b7-b644-85298adf5bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_anaitwa_ambacho-anaitwa-mwilini"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" anaitwa"," userResponse":" anaitwa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786838109","data":{"timestamp":" 946786838109"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_071828"," gameId":" cc0c032e-61dc-48b7-b644-85298adf5bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_gingile_akadeli-gingile-kuogopa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" gingile"," userResponse":" gingile"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.wrd:wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786843884","data":{"timestamp":" 946786843884"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_071828"," gameId":" cc0c032e-61dc-48b7-b644-85298adf5bca"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.wrd_wrd.7.lc.rand.stat.show.7"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_gingile_akadeli-gingile-kuogopa"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786884719","data":{"timestamp":" 946786884719"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_071828"," gameId":" 70c984e5-9f7a-4843-b75c-834940254fe8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_7-8-9"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786893555","data":{"timestamp":" 946786893554"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_071828"," gameId":" 70c984e5-9f7a-4843-b75c-834940254fe8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-3"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786900362","data":{"timestamp":" 946786900362"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_071828"," gameId":" 70c984e5-9f7a-4843-b75c-834940254fe8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_6-4-5"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946786916779","data":{"timestamp":" 946786916779"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000102_071828"," gameId":" 70c984e5-9f7a-4843-b75c-834940254fe8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.rand.ADD-1D-V.2__it_1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_6-9-4"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}